howtocleanstuff.net 2018-11-23

# Privacy Policy » How To Clean Stuff.net

Hi! The section below is our privacy statement. It tells you what information we collect about you and how we use it. It should be pretty easy to understand, but if you have any questions about it please contact us [here](http://www.howtocleanstuff.net/contact-us/) and we’d be happy to explain anything to you in plain English.

The short version is: We collect only the information you freely give us, and we use it only to improve the site. We currently do not send out emails to our users unless requested, and we never sell your information to other companies. You will not be spammed by us!

## Privacy Policy Statement

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](http://g.ezoic.net/privacy/howtocleanstuff.net).  

This is the website of HowToCleanStuff.net.

Our postal address is:

146 Sunset Pl STE 144  
Sequim, WA 98382

You can contact us through [this form  
](http://www.howtocleanstuff.net/contact-us/)or by telephone at +1 210-748-7543

For every visitor that comes to our site, our server recognizes only the visitor’s domain name, but not the e-mail address.

We only collect the domain name, the e-mail addresses of those who post tips and suggestions to our site, the e-mail addresses of anyone who communicates with us through e-mail, aggregate information on the pages that consumers access, and information volunteered freely by the visitor, like survey data and/or registrations.

The information we collect is only used to improve the content of our website and we currently do not send out newsletters or advertising by email.

Cookies are used to store visitors’ preferences.

If you give us your postal address online you will only receive responses in regard to the information you requested.

People who supply us with telephone numbers on-line will receive telephone contact from us only in regard to the purpose specified when the person submitted the number. We do not share visitor information with any outside entities.

To bring you special offers that are of interest to you personally, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place advertisements on our pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of our advertiser, Google [here](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html).

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will use for these new practices only on data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, please contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

Thank you.
